marketingonline.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy - Marketing Online

  1. Information We Collect on Our Own Behalf.

**(a)** Our Service: We may collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, phone number, email address, or similar, when you register for an account. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information. When you use the Marketing Online Service or if you visit our websites, we may receive certain information about you as described below. We do not send any promotional emails; however, we may send you service related emails related to your account. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by canceling your account.

**(b)** Cookies And Tracking Technologies: Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Marketing Online. These technologies may be used in analyzing trends, administering the Sites, tracking your movements around the Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We use cookies to remember users’ settings as well as for authentication and analytics. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Sites, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Sites may be limited. We also use Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Google AdWords (Event/Conversion Tracking), LinkedIn (Event/Conversion Tracking), Facebook (Event/Conversion Tracking), and Twitter (Event/Conversion Tracking). Some or all of these tools may be used to track information about your behavior on our website depending on your region. For more information or to opt-out, please visit the respective website(s) of these vendors or contact us at [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com).

  2. Information We Collect on Behalf of Our Customers.

**(a)** Our Service. We collect data on behalf of our customers who use the Marketing Online Service (by embedding our code on their websites) on the behavior of visitors of our customers’ websites or mobile applications. When you visit such websites or mobile applications, we may receive certain information about your behavior including ser activity, page content, click/touch, movement, scroll, and keystroke activity (in some cases). If you are located in Europe, your IP address, keystroke activity, and personal information are never stored or shared with any third-parties.

**(b)** Information Related To Data Collected For Our Customers: Marketing Online collects information under the direction of its customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose data it may process. If you are a client of one of our current customers and would no longer like to be tracked by such customer, please contact the respective customer directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.

**(c)** Access And Retention Of Data Controlled By Our Customers: An individual who is a current or former Marketing Online customer who seeks access or wishes to correct, amend or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com). An individual who is a client of a current or former Marketing Online customer who seeks access or wishes to correct, amend or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to to the respective customer first and then, if no response is obtained or such response is not satisfactory, should contact [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com). If we receive a request under this provision, we will acknowledge it within 10 business days and handle it promptly.

  3. We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide our services. Marketing Online will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
  4. Information We Collect on Behalf of Third Parties.

Cookies And Tracking Technologies: Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by our partners, affiliates, analytics or service providers. These technologies may be used in analyzing trends, administering the Sites, tracking your movements around the Sites and to gather demographic information about our userbase as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by such companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

  5. How We Use Your Information.

**(a)** We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our Sites and the Marketing Online Service and to respond to your questions and concerns. The legal basis is art. 6(1)(f) of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

**(b)** If you have given your consent, we use the information that we collect to send you marketing communications in our newsletter. The legal basis is art. 6(1)(a) of GDPR.

**(c)** We also use the information that we collect to help our customers improve their website(s).

  6. How We Share Your Information.

**(a)** Personally Identifiable Information: Marketing Online will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Marketing Online (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). Any personally identifiable information you elect to make publicly available on our Sites or the Marketing Online Service, such as posting comments on our blog page, will be available to others. If you remove information that you have made public on our Sites or the Marketing Online Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our Sites or the Marketing Online Service, or if other users have copied or saved that information. Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

**(b)** Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Marketing Online Services and those of our partners. Our partners also have the option to publish the results for their websites on the Marketing Online Service. Such results consist solely of non-personally identifiable information. If you choose to publish such results on the Marketing Online Service or Site, you understand and agree that this information, along with any personally identifiable information you choose to make available in connection with such results, will be made publicly available. By publishing your results on the Marketing Online Service or Site, you agree that you have obtained all necessary consents to make such information public and that doing so will not violate any laws. If you remove information that you have made public on the Marketing Online Service or Site, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Marketing Online Service or Site, or if other users have copied or saved that information. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.

**(c)** Instances Where We Are Required To Share Your Information: Marketing Online will disclose your information where required to do so by law, if subject to subpoena or other legal proceeding or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Marketing Online, our users or others.

**(d)** What Happens In The Event Of A Change Of Control: We may buy or sell/divest/transfer the company (including any shares in the company), or any combination of its products, services, assets and/or businesses. Your information such as customer names and email addresses, and other User information related to the Marketing Online Service may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred in these types of transactions. We may also sell, assign or otherwise transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, reorganizations, liquidations, similar transactions or proceedings involving all or a portion of the company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**(e)** Testimonials: We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com).

  7. Storage and Processing. Your information collected through the Marketing Online Service may be stored and processed in the United States, Europe, or any other country in which Marketing Online or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Marketing Online may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or European Econonmic Area, please note that we will not transfer information, including personal data, to a country outside of the European Union or European Economic Area.
  8. How We Protect Your Information. Marketing Online is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Marketing Online or guarantee that your information on the Marketing Online Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. When you enter sensitive information (such as log in credentials) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can contact us at [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com). We use an outside help platform, and a credit card processing company to bill you if you purchase services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
  9. Compromise of Personal Information. In the event that personal information is compromised as a breach of security, Marketing Online will promptly notify our customers in compliance with applicable law.
  10. Children’s Privacy. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Marketing Online does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@marketingonline.com](mailto:support@marketingonline.com)
  11. Notification Procedures. It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by Marketing Online in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.
  12. Links to Other Web Sites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Marketing Online Service or Sites, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Marketing Online Service or Sites to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.
  13. Social Media Widgets: Our Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and other widgets, that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the organization providing it.
  14. Changes to Our Privacy Policy. All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we change the policy in a material manner, we will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site, prior to the change becoming effective and update the ‘effective date’ at the top of this page.
